华纳兄   弟影业
向为执行公务而献出
生命的旧金山警察致敬
旧金山警察局
向为执行公务而献出
生命的旧金山警察致敬
旧金山警察局
克林特·伊斯特伍德
辣手神探
天啊
Jesus!
致旧金山市
"To the city of San Francisco.
付我十万美元
I will enjoy killing one person every day...
否则每天杀一人
...until you pay me one hundred thousand dollars.
若同意 在明早的
If you agree, say so tomorrow morning...
"旧金山年史报"个人栏通知我
...at personal column, San Francisco Chronicle...
我会安排见面
...and I will set up meeting.
若见不到答复 下一目标
If I do not hear from you...
将会是一个天主教士或是
...it'll be my next pleasure to kill a Catholic priest or a..."
署名 天蝎
"Scorpio."
他们到底想干什么
What goes on in their minds?
疯子
Kooks.
我上哪去弄十万美元
Where the hell does he expect me to find a hundred thousand dollars?
你不打算给钱对吗 市长先生
You're not thinking of paying him, are you, Mr. Mayor?
旧金山市政府绝不付钱给罪犯
The City of San Francisco does not pay criminals not to commit crimes.
我要把钱给警察局
Instead, we pay a police department.
谁负责这个案子
Chief, who's in charge of this case?
卡拉汉警官 他就在外面
Inspector Callahan. He's outside.
请卡拉汉警官进来
Send Inspector Callahan in.
卡拉汉
Callahan?
市长先生 这是卡拉汉警官
Mr. Mayor, Inspector Callahan.
好
All right.
咱们谈谈
Let's have it.
- 谈什么 - 你的报告 你在做什么
- Have what? - Your report. What have you been doing?
在过去45分钟里
For the past 3/4 hour...
我一直坐在外边等你召见
...I've been sitting on my ass waiting on you.
哈里 你在跟市长说话
Damn it, Harry. It's the mayor you're talking to.
请坐 卡拉汉警官
Won't you sit down, Inspector Callahan?
有个疯子在外面乱跑
There's a madman loose.
我问你都做了些什么
I've asked you what's being done. Fair enough?
我们查了十几个可疑人的档案
We've got a dozen men checking identification files.
勒索者 喜欢在楼顶溜达的人
Checking on all known extortionists, rooftop prowlers...
玩枪的疯子和有窥视癖的
...rifle nuts, peepers...
市长先生
Mr. Mayor?
已安排楼顶监视哨和 直升机巡逻
We've arranged for rooftop surveillance and helicopters...
特别是天主教堂和 学校附近
...especially around the Catholic churches and schools...
及黑人区
...and in the black area.
我们正检测弹壳上的弹道
Ballistics is checking on the slug.
确认是306步枪
We're sure it's a 30-06.
7条阳堂线 右手抠动板机
Seven lands and grooves, right-hand twist...
用电脑查找所有天蝎座的人
We're running a computer check...
出生日期在10月23日
...on everybody in the files whose birthday falls between...
至11月21日之间的人
...October 23 and November 21.
为什么
Why?
天蝎座的当地人
Natives of Scorpio.
谢谢 警官
Thank you, inspector.
你们对别人提起过这封信吗
Have you mentioned this note to anyone?
你呢
How about you?
没有
Nobody.
你妻子呢 你的亲近的人呢
Your wife, sweetheart? Press?
没有
Nobody.
把信交给"年史报"
All right. Give the message to the Chronicle.
我们同意付钱 跟他说需要时间筹集这笔钱
We'll pay. But we need time to get the money together.
等等
Wait a minute. Do I get this right?
你是想跟他玩游戏
You'll play this creep's game?
这会给我们一点喘息时间
It'll give us breathing space.
会有人被杀
It might get somebody killed.
让我去见他
Let me meet with the son of a bitch!
不行 你会没命的
Nope, none of that. We would end up with a real bloodbath.
我同意局长的意见 按我说的做
I agree with the chief. We'll do it this way.
谢谢市长先生 哈里 走吧
Thank you, Mr. Mayor. Come on, Callahan, let's go.
我不想看见你惹麻烦 明白吗
I don't want trouble, like you had last year in the Fillmore district.
这是我的原则
That's my policy.
明白 一流氓追赶妇女企图强奸
When an adult male is chasing a female...
我开枪宰了他 这是我的原则
...with intent to commit rape, I shoot the bastard. That's my policy.
企图
Intent?
你怎么能断定
How did you establish that?
裸体男人手里拿着 屠刀追赶妇女
When a naked man chases a woman in an alley with a knife and a hard-on...
我想他不会是在 为红十字会募捐
...I figure he isn't out collecting for the Red Cross.
我想他说的有道理
I think he's got a point.
- 卡拉汉警官 - 杰斐
- Inspector Callahan. - Jaffe.
照常
Usual.
午饭还是晚饭
Usual lunch, or usual dinner?
有什么区别吗
What difference does it make?
区别不大
Not much.
杰斐
Hey, Jaffe...
那棕色福特还停在银行对面
...is that tan Ford still in front of the bank?
棕色福特
Tan Ford?
是的
Yeah, tan Ford.
没熄火
Engine running?
我怎么知道
I don't know. How can I tell?
- 排气管冒着烟 - 太糟糕了
- Exhaust fumes out of the tailpipe. - That's awful!
环境污染
Look at that pollution.
帮个忙
Do me a favor, will you?
帮忙打这个电话
Call this telephone number.
警察局
Police Department?
就说卡拉汉警官认为
Tell them Inspector Callahan thinks there's a...
这家银行里有情况
...two-eleven in progress at the bank. Got it?
明白了
Got it.
告诉他们正在进行
Be sure and tell them it's in progress, right?
正在进行 是长官
In progress. Yes, sir.
等着瞧吧 警察马上就到
Now, if they'll just wait till the cavalry arrives.
妈的
Shit!
站住
Halt!
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
他打了6枪还是5枪
Did he fire six shots or only five?
说实话我太兴奋早就忘了
To tell the truth, in the excitement I kind of lost track myself.
这是最厉害的手枪
This is a.44 Magnum, the most powerful handgun in the world...
能把你的脑袋打飞
...and would blow your head clean off...
你要问自己"我走运吗"
...you've got to ask yourself one question: "Do I feel lucky?"
你走运吗
Well, do you, punk?
我必须知道
I got to know.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
看来我们能保住这条腿
It looks like we can save that leg.
它不能扔下我不管
I've got a couple under my knee.
没考虑过换个工作
Ever consider another line of work?
谢谢你 史蒂夫
I really appreciate this, Steve.
别客气 咱们是朋友 从小一起玩大
We Potrero Hill boys have to stick together.
现在不玩了
Nothing fancy, now.
你只知道镊子红药水
Just a little tweezers and Mercurochrome.
我去过警察局教你 怎样让犯人屈打成招吗
Do I tell you how to beat a confession out of a prisoner?
- 快点 我还有事 - 可能有点不舒服
- I haven't got all night. - You might experience discomfort.
不过没关系 你老婆能解决问题
But if you do, just have your wife fix a...
对不起
Sorry, Harry.
- 你用这个干嘛 - 把你的裤子剪开
- What will you do with those? - Cut your pants off.
- 不 还是脱下来 - 会很疼
- No. We'll pull them off. - It'll hurt.
这裤子29块5
For $29.50, let it hurt.
你要是害羞就转过身去
You can turn your back if you're embarrassed.
- 早上好 警官 - 玛丽娅
- Good morning, inspector. - Maria.
你找我
You wanted to see me, lieutenant?
对 你什么时候理的发
When the hell you going to get a haircut?
不记得了
Whenever you do.
我查线索到凌晨3点
Who's got time? I was up till 3 a.m. Checking the search patterns.
- 算你加班 - 天天如此
- Put in for overtime. - That'll be the day.
昨天你干得不错 局长很高兴
You made a good pinch. Chief was pleased.
- 真的? - 他让我转告你 干得漂亮
- He was? - He said to say, "Well done!"
我激动万分
I can't tell you how moved I am.
我向你转达祝贺
I pass along a compliment...
你该礼貌点 说声谢谢你死不了
...you could be a little polite. It might not kill you to say thanks.
被提升我才说谢谢
I'd rather say thanks to a raise.
来听通报 芝加哥来的一个疯子
Harry, check communications. Something from Chicago. A gun nut.
- 我马上去办 - 等等
- I'll get right on it. - Now wait a minute!
我找了个人跟着你
I'm putting somebody with you.
- 你说什么 - 你需要个新搭档
- What are you talking about? - You need a partner.
- 我现在的搭档怎么了 - 没事 只是躺在医院里
- What's wrong with the one I've got? - He's in the hospital!
- 他一两星期就会出院 - 向齐科问声好
- He'll be out in a few weeks. - Say hello to Chico Gonzales.
- 他跟你一起工作 - 别开玩笑了
- He'll be working with you. - You must be kidding.
我没时间和新人打交道
I have no time to break in newcomers.
- 你帮这孩子一个忙 - 什么意思
- Why don't you do this boy a favor? - What do you mean?
你知道做我的搭档意味着什么 德基克挨了一枪住在医院
You know what happens to guys I worked with. Deitzick's in the hospital...
凡杜奇死了
...and Fanduchi's dead.
那又怎么样
So?
若需要搭档我自己会找
If I need a partner, I'll get me one who knows what he's doing.
弗兰克怎么样
What about De Georgio?
不行
No way!
要么和他一起干要么别干
You work with Gonzales or you don't work.
这事就这么定了 明白吗
Straight from the fifth floor. Got it?
明白
I got it.
叫迪乔吉奥来一趟
If you see De Georgio, send him in here!
是本地人吗
You from around here?
是 不过上大学在圣约瑟
Yeah, but I went to San Jose State.
- 打球吗 - 不 我打拳 轻重量级
- Play ball? - No, I boxed. Light heavyweight.
我最需要的就是大学生
Just what I need is a college boy.
- 找到一点让你喜欢的东西吗 - 还早
- Found anything you like about me yet? - It's early yet.
- 拿到学位了 - 社会学
- Get your degree? - Sociology.
- 你前途远大 如果你活着 - 我争取
- Sociology! You'll go far, if you live. - I intend to.
卡拉汉警官
Inspector Callahan.
别让你的学位杀了你 因为我有责任跟你一起被杀掉
Don't let your degree get you killed. I'm liable to get killed with you.
我会记住的
I'll remember that.
- 大英雄 昨天干得漂亮 - 布莱斯勒要见你
- Hero! Nice work yesterday. - Fatso! Bressler wants to see you.
你真可爱 哈里
You're a sweet man, Harry.
有个问题 卡拉汉警官
There is one question, Inspector Callahan.
他们为什么叫你肮脏的哈里
Why do they call you Dirty Harry?
这是哈里的一个特点
That's one thing about our Harry.
他不会喜欢什么
Doesn't play favorites.
他讨厌所有人 英国人 爱尔兰人 希腊人 意大利人
Harry hates everybody: Limeys, micks, hebes, dagos, niggers, honkies, chinks.
黑人白人亚洲人全在内
You name it.
- 他觉得墨西哥人怎么样 - 问他吧
- How does he feel about Mexicans? - Ask him!
特别是西班牙人
Especially spics.
致天蝎 我们同意付款 但需时间筹集 请耐心等待
那边楼顶上有个人
Hey! There's a guy on the roof over there!
华盛顿广场的斯托克顿街
On Stockton Street by Washington Square.
楼顶上的人
You, on the roof!
你
You, there!
停止一切活动
Yes, you. Stop what you're doing.
转过身 举起手
Turn around and put your hands in the air.
他们怎么让他溜走了
I don 't know how the helicopter boys lost him!
怎么会没看见他往哪跑了
How could they let him get out without seeing him?
他们可能在聊天而不是在观察
They were probably talking instead of looking, like they were supposed to.
他们经常这样
That's possible.
各单位注意
Attention, all units.
声音开大一点
Turn that thing up louder.
上次在华盛顿广场附近 见到的屋顶枪手
Prowler last seen in the vicinity
现在已有消息
of Washington Square.
一成年男性
He is an adult male.
白人 重复 一名成人男性白人
Caucasian. Repeat, adult male Caucasian.
身穿棕斜纹布裤
When last seen, he was wearing tan chinos...
浅蓝色衬衫 棕色外套或毛衣戴黑手套
... pale blue shirt, brown coat or sweater, dark gloves.
拿一只棕色皮箱
He had a tan suitcase...
内可能有306步枪 此人涉嫌谋杀被通缉
... which probably contains a 30-06 rifle. He's wanted...
这些疯子 应该把他们一网打尽
Those loonies! They ought to throw a net over the whole bunch!
我明白你的意思
I know what you mean.
- 在那里 - 什么
- There! - What?
棕色皮箱
Tan suitcase.
- 在哪里 - 不见了
- Where? - I lost him.
在那里
There he goes, over there.
那皮箱不是棕色的吗
Does that bag look tan?
不知道 我没看见那个混蛋
I don't know, I haven't even seen him yet.
向左拐
Go to Filbert and hang a left.
当心前面有人
Look out for these people!
- 混蛋 - 走开
- Fruitcake! - Get out of the way, hammerhead!
我肯定看见了
It was a tan suitcase. I know it was.
在那里
I saw him.
- 就在那边 - 我看见了
- There he is. - I see him.
2号车 10-32在那辆
Car 2, the license number...
雪佛兰车里 车牌号是科罗拉多州的
... at 10-32 on that Chevrolet, Colorado plates.
- 你打算怎么办 - 你去 另一个出口我从这里进去
- How do you want to work this? - Find another entrance. I'll go here.
2号车 是雪佛兰车什么型号的
Car 2, what's the model of that Chevrolet?
2号车 是黑斑羚车
Car 2. It's an Impala convertible.
你可以删去那辆10-25 这里有三辆车
You can cancel that 10-25. Three cars here.
家里有人吗
Anybody home?
- 给你带了好东西 - 太好了让我看看
- I brought you a nice present. - Let me see it.
真漂亮 来帮我穿上
It's beautiful! Why don't you go get a nice container of egg rolls?
你这个流氓大饱眼福了吧
You getting an eyeful?
你这个家伙
You goddamn pie hawker!
- 我们该报警 - 我是警察 住手 都别动
- We should call the police. - I am a police...
靠墙站好
Up against the wall. Right now! Move.
- 放他们走 - 放他们走?
- Let them go. - Let them go?
- 放他们走 - 他们袭击警官
- You heard me. - They assaulted a police officer.
什么警官 他站在垃圾筒上
A police officer! He was standing on a can peeking in...
偷看玛丽和她的男友
...on Hot Mary and her boyfriend!
住嘴 快滚
Beat it. Get out of here.
- 那个拎皮箱的人呢 - 盯错人了
- How about the man with the suitcase? - Wrong number.
我想我明白了
I just had another thought.
明白什么了
Yeah? About what?
他们为什么叫你肮脏的哈里
About why they call you Dirty Harry.
71号
Inspector 71.
请回答71号
Inspector 71. Please respond to your call.
71号听到了吗
Inspector 71. Do you read me?
- 我是71号 - 发现有人劫持
- This is Inspector 71. - I've got an 8-0-4 in progress.
波克特克大街加里福尼亚大楼
California Hall at Polk and Turk streets.
我们马上就到
10-4. We're on our way.
上面有个疯子
It's some idiot.
哪里 我看不到他
Where? I don't see him.
- 他在那里- 我看到了
- There he is. - Yeah. Now I see him.
我看到10-29和10-28
I have a 10-29 and a 10-28.
在贝克街600号 在雪佛兰车上
In 600 block of Baker. On a Chevrolet.
加州车牌号 DCV472
California license D-dog, C-Charles, V-Victor 4-7-2.
抱歉把你们叫来
We thought it was your sniper,
以为是你们要找的人 结果是个企图自杀的家伙
but it turned out to be a suicide attempt.
- 有人劝过他吗 - 劝过 可不管用 好在你来了
- Anybody try to talk him down? - Yeah, no luck. But now you're here...
- 你是说我上去 - 希望你能
- You mean, I go up. - We'd sure appreciate it.
看着他 他会受伤害的
Look at him, he'll get hurt.
你别想杀我
Don't you try to get me!
不是我 是你要杀你自己
Not me. You're the one who wants to get yourself killed. Not me.
你们这些人总是这样
Always happens with you guys. The last minute you want to...
总想找个伴一块死 你跳吧我可不跳
...grab onto somebody, take somebody with you. Down you go. Not me!
你不想抓住我吗
Won't you try to grab me?
我有个朋友几年前 被跳楼人抓住
A friend of mine was up about 20 floors with a jumper a few years ago.
从20层楼上一起掉下去
The jumper grabbed him and they went off.
摔在人行道上
Mashed all over.
分不清胳膊是谁的腿是谁的
Couldn't tell which legs was with which, which arms with which...
惨不忍睹我差点昏过去
It was a terrible mess. I tell you, I almost threw up myself.
- 我只想知道你的名字和住址 - 干嘛
- I'd just like your name and address. - Why?
下去后你会摔得一遢糊涂
It's a mess down there afterwards! It makes identification impossible.
没法辨认你的身份 即使找到你的驾照
Even if they find your driver's license!
上面也都是血
All that blood!
我要吐
I think I'm going to puke!
别干傻事 下面的人都在看
Don't do that, son. All those people down there looking up.
消防队长也在看 你看他的脸
The fire chief looking up. With his face...
你这个兔崽子
You bastard!
把担架送来
Get the stretcher up here.
现在知道我 为什么叫肮脏的哈里了
Now you know why I'm called Dirty Harry.
每件赃活都得我去干
Every dirty job that comes along.
71号警官听见了请回答
Inspector 71.
我是71号警官
This is Inspector 71.
西尔拉拐角处一个男孩黑人
Got something for you. Corner of Sierra and Texas. A young boy, Negro.
他怎么了
What about him?
射中脸部半个脸打飞了
Shot in the face. Blew part of it away.
有人知道他是谁吗
Anybody know who the boy is?
他叫查理 拉塞尔
His name was Charlie Russell.
我是他妈妈
I'm his mother.
他只有10岁
He's only 10 years old.
警官 天啊
Inspector, this officer... Oh, Jesus Christ!
去问问孩子的母亲
You'd better go check on the mother.
有什么情况
What do you have?
发现36毫米子弹壳
That 30-06 shell casing.
他来过这里
He was up here all right.
欢迎加入刑侦处
Welcome to Homicide.
为警察设计蓝制服的那个人
The man who designed blue serge uniforms for police departments...
不得不卖掉这东西维持生计
...has to sell these for a living!
458弹药筒
.458 Magnum?
- 足以打死大象 - 是的
- This thing will stop an elephant. - Yeah.
- 显然你喜欢用刀 - 我只能带刀
- Apparently you like a little edge. - All I can get, sir.
他不是大象不是动物记住这点
He's no elephant, Harry. He's no animal of any kind.
怎么样 队长
What have you got, lieutenant?
照你的吩咐 蓝旗代表今晚参加行动的小组
The blue flags represent the units that will be on duty by dark tonight.
- 两班倒 算加班 - 只有夜里需要
- Double shifts and overtime. - At nighttime.
白天有直升飞机他不敢上楼顶
Daylight, the helicopters will keep him off the roofs.
我已命令所有小组 尽量暴露自己
We're going for high visibility. Units will make themselves very noticeable.
- 除了这个地方 北海滨地区是给他留着的
- Except here. - Right. The North Beach area.
你给自己找好位置了吗
We're saving that for him.
- 找到好的监视位置没有 - 找到了
- Have you found a good stakeout? - I think so.
一座大楼能看见昨天发现 他的那个楼顶
It's a building that overlooks the roof where they spotted him yesterday.
有什么不妥吗
Something bothering you?
- 没有 - 说出来 这里全是朋友
- Nothing. - Speak up. You're among friends here.
我们没把握他会回到原地
It seems a long shot that he'd come back to the same roof.
旧金山有很多楼顶
There are a lot of rooftops in San Francisco.
大部分都锁上了 这栋是专门为他留着的
Most of them are locked. This particular one'll be open for him.
这些疯子有固定的行为模式
These sick guys have behavior patterns.
有罪犯抢劫 同一个商店三四次
We know they'll rob the very same store 3, 4 times in a row.
为了满足自我
Must appeal to their superego or something.
天蝎又行动了
Scorpio strikes again.
他们喜欢这种感觉
They like that feeling.
他可能选择这楼顶另有原因
There's one other reason why he might pick the same rooftop.
这里可以清楚地看到圣彼德 和圣保罗教堂
He's got a clear view of the St. Peter and Paul's Church.
今晚要举行一个祷告仪式
And they're having a novena tonight.
说下去
Go on.
那封信里他威胁说要杀一个 天主教牧师和一个黑人
The note. He threatened to kill a priest or a Negro.
拉塞尔就是这个黑人
The Russell boy was black.
他会想还欠一个牧师
He may just figure he owes himself a padre.
71警官
Inspector 71.
我已到达预定位置开始监视
We're in position to start our surveillance.
那牧师怎么样
How about the priest?
- 他知道自己是诱饵 - 知道 他愿意
- He knows he's being set up for bait? - Yeah, he wanted to.
我们说了有个志原者可以替他
We told him we had a volunteer willing to take his place.
谁
Who?
你猜不着
Never guess.
我知道 欢迎加入刑侦处
Yeah, I know. Welcome to Homicide.
你要多活一会儿 哈里
You owe it to yourself to live a little, Harry.
他上钩了
Son of a bitch took the bait!
我说开始你用手电筒照他
When I say "now," hit him with the light.
开始
Now!
- 你没事吧 - 我想没事
- You all right? - I think so.
快叫救护车
Call an ambulance.
科林斯永远不知道什么击中了
Collins never knew what hit him.
走开 让一让
Let's go. Clear the alley. There's nothing to see.
他向北海滨地区跑了
Call headquarters. He's loose in North Beach.
封锁这个地区快行动 又一轮新游戏
It's a whole new ball game, fellows.
他抓了一个14岁的女孩
He grabbed a 14-year-old girl.
叫安尼马丽 迪肯
Ann Mary Deacon.
防爆队今早接到电话 金门公园门口发现可疑物品
The bomb squad got a call. Suspicious object in Golden Gate Park.
写着市长收 化验室转给 我们里面夹着这封
It was addressed to the mayor. The lab sent it to us, with this letter inside.
安妮马丽 迪肯被活埋
"Ann Mary Deacon, buried alive."
可怜的姑娘昨晚 看电影再没回来
The poor kid went to the movies last night and never came home.
我这么做是被旧金山警察逼的
"Double-crossing San Francisco police made me do this.
赎金两百万只要 十元二十元旧钞
Now ransom $200,000, in used tens and twenties.
一个人带着黄皮包
One man with yellow bag.
到格林东码头
South side Marina. Green East Harbor.
晚上九点
9 p.m.
她有氧气能维持到明早三点
She has oxygen till 3 a.m. Tomorrow.
红色的内裤和胸罩
Red panties and bra. Nice tits.
左腿有胎记
Mole on left thigh. Anything cute and you'll force me to let girl die...
若耍花招就慢慢杀死她 署名天蝎
...of slow suffocation. Signed, Scorpio."
还有别的吗
Anything else?
她母亲认识这胸罩和她的头发
The mother identified the bra... ...the hank of hair...
还有
...and that.
她的牙医认出这个
The dentist identified that.
是用钳子拔出来的
Said it was pulled out with a pair of pliers.
你知道她死了对吗
You know she's dead.
信上说她能活到明早三点
All I know is the letter says she'll be alive until 3 a.m.
市长去筹款了
The mayor's out trying to put the money together now.
他会尽最大努力
He's using up a lot of favors.
他想付钱
He wants to pay.
不耍花招
No tricks.
需要个送钱的人你愿意干吗
We need a bag man. You want the job?
那好 就是你了
You got it.
- 下午六点到局长办公室 - 知道了
- Be in the chief's office at 6 p.m. - All right.
- 那我呢 - 没你的份
- Wait a minute. What about me? - You're out.
一个掩护都没有
No cover? Not even one man?
你肯定这样能行
Sure that's how to do it?
不能肯定但这是我的命令
I'm not sure! But those are my orders. All right?
难怪叫他肮脏的哈里 所有的屁股都是他一个人擦
No wonder they call him Dirty Harry. He gets the shit end of the stick.
再说一个字我砍掉你的脚
One more word and you're chopped off at the ankles.
折衷一下好吗 今晚放他们的
Al, let's split the difference. Give him the night off.
你们两个都给我出去
Get the hell out of here, both of you.
试音1 2 3
Testing 1, 2, 3...
- 你喊什么 - 小声说就行
- What are you yelling for? - All you have to do is whisper.
玛丽有只小羊 羊毛又白又长
"Mary had a little lamb, its fleece as white as snow."
行了 好多了
Okay, that's better.
两三个街区内没问题 进隧道就别指望了
It's good for 2 or 3 blocks. But in a tunnel...
算了
...forget it.
怎么谢你
All right, Sid. What do I owe you?
别把它弄坏了
Bring it back in one piece.
20万美元
$200,000.
数一数签个字
Count it and sign for it.
你数过了吗
Did you count it out?
你数过了吗 局长
Did you count it, chief?
那不是我的事
It's not my responsibility.
早就知道我能靠警方发财
Always knew I'd get rich on the police force.
小心别让别人抢走了
Just make sure nobody takes it away from you.
鬼知道他将怎么与你联系 他可能让你满城跑
God knows how he'll contact you. He'll probably run you all over town.
他让你去哪你就去哪 让你干什么就干什么
Go where you're told. Do what you're told.
- 严格按计划做 明白吗 - 明白
- Play it straight down the line. Okay? - Okay.
别耍小聪明 别突发奇想
Nothing cute. Nothing fancy.
去交赎金然后回来报告
Just pay the ransom money and report back here.
好 借我胶带用用不介意吧
Would you mind if I borrowed a little Scotch tape?
警官用这种武器有点让人厌恶
It's disgusting that a police officer should know how to use that weapon.
- 你有没有带黄色箱子 - 就在我手上
- You got a yellow suitcase? - Yeah, I got it right with me.
- 你叫什么 - 卡拉汉
- What's your name? - Callahan.
- 干什么的 - 警官
- What are you? - Police officer.
喂 喂
Hello?
好吧 警官
All right, police officer...
游戏这么玩
... this is how we play.
你在城里走一圈 确保你是一个人
I bounce you all over town to make sure you're alone.
若发现有别人 那姑娘就死定了
If I even think you're being followed, the girl dies.
你若跟任何人说话 哪怕是路灯下撒尿的哈巴狗
If you talk to anyone, even if it's a Pekinese pissing on a lamppost...
我就杀了她
... the girl dies.
- 姑娘没事吧 - 闭嘴
- Is the girl okay? - Just shut up and listen.
不许用车
No car.
你的时间有限 到另一个电话亭电话铃响4次
I give you some time to go from phone booth to phone booth.
4声后你没接我就挂掉
I ring 4 times. You don 't answer by the fourth ring...
游戏到此结束
... that's the end of the game.
那姑娘没命
The girl dies.
你的表几点了
What time you got?
- 九点半 听我说 - 你听我说
- 9:30. Now listen... - You listen.
我盯着你
I'm watching you.
不是从头到尾 可你不知道我在
Not all the time, but you'll never know when or where.
现在你以最快速度到森林山车 明白吗
Now get to Forest Hills Station as fast as you can. Understand?
- 明白 - 希望你不是傻瓜
- Yeah. - I hope you're not stupid.
下楼乘下一班车
Downstairs. Take the "K" car.
在教堂20大街路口下车 快点 否则来不及了
Get off at Church and 20th. Hurry up, or you'll blow it.
听上去你一点也不累 很好
You sound like you had a good rest.
这回让你好好跑一跑
You'll need it. I'm going to give you a nice little run this time.
你最好能跑到 否则那姑娘就没命
You better make it, because if you don 't, dead girl!
公用电话 汉堡售货亭 水上公园
Public phone, hamburger stand, Aquatic Park.
"快点 臭猪"
Hubba-hubba-hubba, pig bastard.
包里装的是什么
What's in the bag, man?
- 快给我滚开 听见没有 - 把包打开
- You dudes get lost now, you hear? - Screw the bag!
快把钱包给我们
Just give us the wallet.
不听我的话 混蛋
You don't listen, do you, asshole?
别接电话
Don't answer that!
- 接电话的是谁 - 只是个老头我从没见过他
- Who picked it up? - Some old guy. Never saw him before.
天哪 齐科 他挂了
Chico, he hung up.
- 知道戴维逊公园吗 - 知道
- You know Mt. Davidson Park? - Yeah.
到十字路口去
Go to the cross.
我在兰斯戴尔街 戴维逊公园门口
I'm at the entrance on Lansdale Street.
我在向前走
I'm going up.
我看见两个人
I see a couple of people.
是两个孩子在亲热
Just a couple of kids necking.
男孩还是女孩
Boys or girls?
我是卡拉汉
I'm Callahan.
叫我艾利斯
My friends call me Alice.
我喜欢挑战
And I will take a dare.
你上次挨揍是什么时候
When was the last time you were busted?
你要是不怀好意我就自杀
If you're a vice, I'll kill myself.
回家去自杀吧
Well, do it at home.
别动
Freeze!
像雕像一样
Just like a statue.
这就对了
That's right.
乱动一下让我不高兴
One wrong move, anything, I don't care.
我就杀了你和那姑娘
I'll kill you and the girl both.
明白吗
Understand?
明白
Yeah.
把包扔下
Drop the bag.
用左手
Left hand.
让我看你的枪
Let's see the gun.
天啊
My!
好大的家伙
That's a big one.
用左手把它扔了
Left hand. Throw it.
慢点
Easy.
把手举起来
Raise your hands.
快举起来
Come on, get them up.
转过身
Now turn.
面向石碑
Face the cross.
把鼻子贴在水泥墙上
Put your nose right up against the cement.
你的手要是再动一下 我就不让你知道那姑娘在哪
You lift that hand once more and I won't let you know where the girl is!
明白我的意思吗
Do we understand each other?
别跟我装死
Don't pass out on me yet! No, no.
No, no. Not yet. Not yet!
别跟我装死 你这个蠢猪
Don't pass out on me yet, you rotten oinker!
明白吗
Do we understand each other?
你若在意那姑娘的死活 就快点回答我 听见了吗
If you care what happens to the girl, you'd better answer me! All right?
仔细听着
Listen to me carefully.
我改变主意了
I've changed my mind.
我要杀了那姑娘
I'm going to let her die.
我真想让你明白
I just wanted you to know that.
明白吗 我只想让你死个明白
You understand? I just wanted to make sure you knew that before I killed you.
再见了 卡拉汉
Goodbye, Callahan!
齐科 别杀他
Chico, don't kill him!
医院说齐科看上去还不错
The hospital report on Gonzales looks okay, chief.
他是个坚强的孩子
Yeah. Well, he's a pretty tough kid.
哈里 卡拉汉 他就在这里
He's right here.
他断了两根肋骨
He's got two cracked ribs.
早上再给他做进一步检查
They want to do some more tests on him in the morning.
那个混蛋把他踢惨了
The son of a bitch really kicked him a couple of beauts.
送他回家
I'm sending him home.
是 局长
Right, chief.
局长说让你滚回家 这是命令
He says beat it! That's an order.
局长问我是否误解了 他的命令
The chief wants to know if I misunderstood his orders.
他问我是白痴还是故意 不听他的命令
Meaning, am I just plain stupid or did I deliberately disobey him?
他想知道冈萨雷斯 怎么会在那里
He wants to know what Gonzales was doing there.
他想知道为什么把事情搞砸了
He wants to know why we screwed everything up.
现在你让我怎么跟他说呢
What am I going to tell him?
干嘛不一开始就告诉他真相
Why don't you start by telling him the truth?
告诉他齐科执行的是我的命令
Tell him Gonzales was obeying orders from a superior. Me.
告诉他你什么都不知道
Tell him you didn't know anything about it.
案子结束后 他想收回 我的徽章 随他的便
When this is over, if he wants my badge, he can have that too.
你这里有酒吗
You wouldn't have a belt of booze around here, would you?
布莱斯勒警官办公室
Lieutenant Bressler's office.
- 接过来 - 什么事
- Put him on. - What is it?
公园诊所说 有个腿上 有刀伤的去他们那里包扎
It's Park Emergency. They just treated a guy who had a knife wound in the leg.
是大夫吗 那家伙长什么样
Yeah, Doctor? What'd this guy look like?
金色长发
Long blond hair...
中等身材 体重约150磅 皮肤苍白
...medium build, about 150 pounds. Pale complexion.
- 他没留名字吗 大夫 - 没有
- He didn't give you his name, Doc? - Nope.
就是留了通常也是假名字
They usually give a phony name.
可我在什么地方见过他
But I've seen him someplace.
请回忆一下 这非常重要
It's important you remember.
有个14岁的女孩快要窒息了
There's a 14-year-old girl who's suffocating.
让我想想
I'm trying to think!
我肯定他就在附近工作
I believe he works around here.
医生请处理一下他的伤 他疼得厉害
Doctor, could you give him something? He's in pain!
好 请等一下
Yes, just a moment.
1个小时之内她就会死
She'll be dead in an hour!
我正在想
I'm trying to remember!
我想起来了
I've got who he is.
有球赛时 他常在体育馆卖节目单
When they had football, he used to sell programs at the stadium.
场地管理员让他住在那里
I think the groundskeeper lets him live there.
- 住在哪里 - 那里
- Live where? - There.
克扎尔体育馆
Kezar Stadium.
非法进入 没搜查证
Illegal entry. No warrant.
看来咱们得爬了
Looks like we climb.
我吃得太饱
Too much linguine.
还是另找条路吧
I'll find another way.
站住
Stop!
不要这样了 你要杀我 不不
Don't do anything more! You tried to kill me!
要帮忙吗 哈里
You need any help?
- 呼吸你的新鲜空气吧 胖子 - 求求你不要
- Go on and get some air, fatso. - Please! No more!
没看见我受伤了吗 你打中我
Can't you see I'm hurt? You shot me! Please, don't!
求你给我找个医生
Let me have a doctor!
给我找个医生 别杀我
Please, get me the doctor! Don't kill me!
那姑娘在哪
The girl, where is she?
你差点杀了我
You tried to kill me!
我真想杀你你早没命了
If I did, your head would be splattered all over this field. Where's the girl?
我要找律师
I want a lawyer.
快说姑娘在哪
I said, where's the girl?
- 我有权请律师 - 姑娘在哪
- I have the right for one. - Where's the girl?
我有权请律师
I have the right to a lawyer!
别伤害我
Don't! Please!
我有权利我要找律师
I have rights. I want a lawyer!
他说有急事
Harry Callahan. He said it was urgent.
地方检察官要见你
Yes, the district attorney has been wanting to talk to you.
- 卡拉汉警官来了 - 请他进来
- It's Inspector Callahan. - Have him come in, please.
请跟我来
Won't you come this way?
- 要咖啡吗 - 不 谢谢
- May I bring you in a cup of coffee? - No, thanks.
马上就完
I'll be done in a minute.
请坐
Have a seat.
刚才在看你的报告
I've just been looking over your arrest report.
非同寻常
A very unusual piece of police work.
真令人惊讶
Really amazing.
我很走运
I had some luck.
你是很走运 因为我没起诉 你带谋杀倾向的攻击
You're lucky I'm not indicting you for assault with intent to commit murder!
谁给你权利可以踹开人家的门 拷打嫌疑人
Where does it say you've got a right to kick down doors, torture suspects?
不向疑犯提供医疗和法律咨询
Deny medical attention and legal counsel? Where have you been?
你没听说过米兰达权利
Does Escobedo ring a bell? Miranda?
那你一定听过第四修正案
You must have heard of the 4th Amendment!
那个人有他的权利
What I'm saying is, that man had rights.
别跟我说什么他的权利
I'm all broken up about that man's rights.
告诉你
You should be. I've got news for you.
他随时可以离开医院
When he's well enough to leave the hospital, he walks.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
他自由了
He's free!
你是说你放了他
You're letting him go?
必须放 我们不能起诉
We have to. We can't try him.
为什么
And why is that?
我不想浪费纳税人50万块钱
Because I'm not wasting 1/2 million tax dollars...
去打一场赢不了的官司
...on a trial we can't possibly win.
我们没有任何证据
The problem is, we don't have any evidence.
- 证据 你管这个叫什么 - 什么都不是
- What do you call that? - I call it nothing.
零
Zero.
弹道检验与这枝枪不相符
You're saying that Ballistics can't match the bullet up to this rifle?
弹道检验帮不了忙
It does not matter what Ballistics can do!
这枪能作个很好的纪念品
This rifle might make a nice souvenir.
- 但它不能成为证据 - 这是谁说的
- But it's inadmissible as evidence! - Who says?
法律
It's the law.
那是什么破法律
Then the law is crazy!
这位是上诉法院班纳曼法官
This is Judge Bannerman of the appellate court.
同时在伯克利大学讲授宪法 我想听听他的意见
He holds classes in constitutional law. I've asked him for an opinion.
大人
Your Honor?
搜查嫌疑人的住处是非法的
In my opinion, the search of the suspect's quarters was illegal.
在那里得到的证据 比如那步枪
Evidence obtained thereby, such as that hunting rifle for instance...
将不被法庭承认
...is inadmissible in court.
你们应该带着搜查证 很抱歉
You should have gotten a search warrant. I'm sorry.
- 可这是法律 - 搜查证 那姑娘快死了
- It's that simple. - Search warrant? A girl was dying!
事实上 那个时候她已经死了
She was, in fact, dead according to the medical report!
可我不知道
But I didn't know that!
法庭将承认警官关心 那姑娘的生命是合法
The court would recognize the officer's legitimate concern for the girl...
但他们不能因此宽恕警官 拷打嫌疑人
...but there is no way they can possibly condone police torture.
所有关于那姑娘的证据 嫌疑人的口供和
All evidence concerning the girl, the suspect's confession...
所有物证
...physical evidence...
都将被拒绝接受
...would have to be excluded.
你们一定有办法判他
There must be something you can get him on!
没有枪和那姑娘当证据
Without the evidence of the gun and the girl?
我不能因他当街 吐痰而判他有罪
I couldn't convict him of spitting on the sidewalk!
第四第五
Now, the suspect's rights...
可能还有第六第十四修正案
...were violated...
赋予疑犯的权利
...under the 4th and 5th...
不受侵犯
...and probably the 6th and 14th Amendments.
可那姑娘的权利呢
And Ann Mary Deacon, what about her rights?
她被强奸后扔进洞里死了 谁替她说话
She's raped and left in a hole to die! Who speaks for her?
地区检察官办公室
The district attorney's office!
相信我
If you'll let us.
我有妻子和3个孩子 我像你一样不想让他逍遥法外
I have a wife and 3 kids. I don't want him on the streets any more than you do.
他不会遛达很久了
He won't be out there long.
你什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
他早晚得撞在我手上
Sooner or later he will stub his toe and I'll be there.
你别再给我们惹麻烦了
This office won't stand for any harassment!
你若认为他会就此罢休 你就是傻瓜 他还会杀人
You're crazy if you think you've heard the last of him. He will kill again.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因为他喜欢
Because he likes it.
你肯定没被跟踪
You sure you weren't tailed?
没有
Yeah.
你真要享受两百块钱的待遇
You really want $200 worth.
每一分钱
Every penny of it.
也许会很舒服
Might as well be comfortable.
来坐下
Go on, sit.
放松
Relax.
别紧张
Take it easy.
马上就好
It's going to be all right.
剩下的还想要吗
You sure you want the rest of it?
每一分钱
Every penny's worth!
你个黑杂种
You black son of a bitch!
这个在屋里
This one's on the house.
一定是他
That's got to be him.
你是说这是旧金山警察干的
Are you claiming that the San Francisco Police did this to you?
我发誓 上帝作证
I swear it. As God is my judge.
他为什么这样对你
Why are they harassing you?
我不知道 他们陷害我杀了迪肯姑娘
They tried to frame me with the murder.
他们还想杀我
And now they're trying to murder me. And look at me!
在证明我有罪之前我是无辜的
I'm innocent until proven guilty and look at what they did to me.
看看他们都对我做了些什么 我走到哪警察就跟到哪
Everywhere I go cops follow me. And just look at me!
我再问个问题
Just a minute, nurse. Let me ask him one more question.
- 你看清那个打你的人了吗 - 看清了
- Did you see who did this to you? - Yes. I did.
知道他是谁吗
Can you identify him?
他叫卡拉汉 刑侦处的警察 叫卡拉汉
His name is Callahan. He's a big cop. Works Homicide. Callahan.
这是4点新闻的重播
Now, that's the rerun from the 4 o'clock news.
之后他给了报纸一份声明
Since then he's given a statement to The Chronicle.
说你一直跟着他还打了他
He claims you've been following him. And beat him up.
这是怎么回事
What about it, Harry?
- 你要我的警徽吗 - 我要你回答
- You want my star? - I want an answer.
你跟踪那人了吗
Have you been following him?
我用业余时间跟踪他
Yeah, I've been following him on my own time.
- 谁都能证明我没有打他 - 怎么证明
- Anybody can tell I didn't do that. - How?
他看上去太好了 那是表演
Because he looks too damn good, that's how!
允许你离开之前必须说清楚
Before I let you go, let's get one thing straight.
我不希望你再监视他
I don't want any more surveillance!
他也同样
Neither does he.
什么意思
What does that mean?
晚安
Good night, sir.
尝尝
Go ahead. Try them.
- 他们做时我一直在吃 - 谢谢
- Guy makes them where I always eat. - Thank you.
我和上面说了咱们做永久搭档
I talked to Bressler about being on with me.
这样你出院知道有地方可去
So you know you got a spot when you get out.
我不知道我会不会回去
I don't know if I am coming back, Harry.
我想了很久
Doing a lot of thinking about it and...
我有教师证书
I have a teaching credential. And I figure...
我图什么
...what for? You know?
- 治疗时间到了 - 你还没决定是吗
- Time for therapy. - You hang in there now.
明天见 亲爱的
See you tomorrow. Same time?
- 是我的错 - 什么
- It's my fault, you know. - What?
他不想离开 我本以为我能接受
His leaving. I thought I could take it.
我太没风度
No class.
- 别这么说- 什么
- Don't ever say that. - What?
不要责备自己
Don't ever low-rate yourself.
作为警官的妻子
What I meant was, whatever it takes to be a cop's wife...
我是不称职的
...I'm just not sure I'm making it.
他很努力 可那些坏蛋
He really tries, and all these bastards...
杀人抢劫
..."pig" this and "pig" that.
他晚上出门时
But maybe it's when I watch him walk out that door at night.
我总在想
And I think...
他若一去不复返可怎么办
...what if it's the last time I see him?
只是我这样吗
Am I the only one?
你妻子不觉得自己要疯了吗
Doesn't it drive your wife crazy?
不
No.
你是说她习惯了
You mean she got used to it?
她永远不会习惯
No, she never did, really.
怎么回事
What, then?
她死了
She's dead.
请原谅
Please, forgive me.
有天晚上她开车回家 一个醉鬼逆行迎面撞上
She was driving home and a drunk crossed the center line.
毫无原因
No reason for it, really.
- 我很难过 - 没事
- I'm so sorry. - That's okay.
告诉齐科
I want you to tell Chico...
他不想干了 我能理解
...that I understand him quitting.
他是对的 这不是你俩的生活
I think he's right. This is no life for you two.
- 那你为什么还要干 - 不知道
- Why do you stay in it, then? - I don't know.
真的不知道
I really don't.
请你给我拿那个
Let me have a fifth of Seagram's. Please.
我的天 你怎么啦
What the hell happened to you?
老婆的哥哥打的
My wife's brother.
我打老婆
I hit her...
他打我
...so he hit me.
常事
Several times.
5.69美元
$5.69.
你就是那个被抢了好几次的人
You're the guy that's been robbed all these times.
我总带着它 就放在这里
14 times the last 3 years.
前两次没费劲就把他们赶跑了
Last 2 times, I sent them out of here on platters.
我的枪法很准
I'm getting to be a pretty good shot.
我总带着它 就放在这里
And I always keep it right here. Right where it's handy.
别 我胆小
Please, I scare easy.
妈的 你这混蛋
Dirty son of a bitch! You pilferer!
再见
Goodbye.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
该下车的快点下啦
Everybody out who gets out here?
校车巡视员 孩子们好
School bus inspector.
巡视员 从没听说过
One minute. I'm not allowed to have anybody...
我是新来的 开车吧
I'm authorizing it, so go.
我不认识你
What are you doing? I don't know you.
你这蠢猪快开车 否则我打烂你的脑袋
Hear me, old hag. Drive or I'll decorate this bus with your brains.
- 去哪里 - 开车 我会告诉你去哪
- Where? - Just get started. I'll tell you where.
大家都高兴点
Let's have some fun now.
谁会唱歌
Who knows a song?
人人都会唱歌 你一定会唱个好听的
Everybody knows a song. You? You must know a beautiful one.
唱吧 唱吧
Come on, sing for us.
市长办公室
- 这位是卡拉汉警官 - 市长在等你们
- Millie, this is Inspector Callahan. - The Mayor is waiting for you.
- 出了什么事 - 那小子又送来一封信
- What's up? - Another note from our boy.
- 他又抓了谁 - 问题是我们还不知道
- Who's he grabbed now? - That's the trouble, we don't know yet.
飞机加满油准备好 半小时内起飞
The jet must be fueled and ready to go in half an hour.
小分队必须是自愿者
Skeleton crew. They must be volunteers.
告诉他们这个人很危险
Tell them the man is dangerous.
今早8点收到的 我来念
I'll read you this note which was delivered at 8:00 this morning.
致旧金山市
"To the City of San Francisco.
你们上次骗了我 我警告你们
You double-crossed me for the last time.
把20万元放在飞机上等候起飞
I'm warning you to have my $200,000 in a jet airplane ready and waiting.
我一点钟给市长办公室打电话
I'll call the Mayor's office at 1:00 and tell you about the hostages...
告诉你们人质的情况 若不照办
...who I will be happy to kill if you don't do...
我很乐意杀掉他们 天蝎
...exactly what I say. Scorpio."
你们做好准备
Better have somebody standing by!
这可能是个假警报 不过别心怀侥幸
I don't think it's a false alarm.
市长先生 二号线有你的电话
There's a call for you on line 2.
我想是你在等的那个人
I think it's the one you've been waiting for.
- 我是市长 - 我从公园街小学请了七个孩子
- It's the Mayor. - I got 7 kids from Park Street School.
校车在我手里
I got the bus and...
好孩子 回到车上去
Come on, honey, now back in the bus. That's a good girl.
司机也在我手里 她就在这里
I got the bus driver. Here she is.
告诉他们
Just tell him.
不是我的错 他拿着枪
Not my fault, he had a gun...
告诉他你的名字
Just your name!
我叫玛塞拉 普拉特
This is Marcella Platt.
你们可以去核实 可我觉得没必要
You can check if you want. But I don 't see any point.
我不是跟你们闹着玩
I'm not bullshitting.
孩子们在我手里 敢跟我耍花招
It's simple. I got the kids. You start screwing around...
孩子们就没命
... the kids start dying.
- 飞机准备好了 - 飞机正在加油 马上就到机场
- The plane ready? - It's being fueled, and ready to go.
你到了就能看见钱
The money will be there by the time you get there.
听好了 我要做一次轻松愉快的旅行
Listen carefully. I will drive along nice and easy.
只有我和孩子
Just me and a busload of kids.
我要从圣弗朗西斯大道 拐上公路 去桑塔罗萨机场
I'll turn off at Sir Francis Drake on my way to Santa Rosa Airport.
我不想看见警察的
I don 't want any police cars...
直升机和警车
... helicopters, whatever.
胆敢跟我玩 孩子们 就会来次愉快的空中旅行
If you play this game by the rules, the kids will have a nice plane ride.
你准备去哪里
Where are you going?
上飞机后我会告诉驾驶员 不许报警
I'll tell the pilot when I get on. No alerts.
我保证你不会受到任何干扰
I guarantee you, you will not be molested in any way.
以我的名誉担保
I give you my word of honor.
玛塞拉 普拉特 核对无误
Marcella Platt. It checks.
卡拉汉 愿意去给他送钱吗
Willing to take the money to him?
你们什么时候才肯面对事实 必须制止这家伙
When will you stop messing around with this guy? He has to be stopped now!
他劫持了一辆坐满孩子的校车 我不能冒这个险
He's got a busload of kids and I can't take that chance.
我已经向他保证 他不会受到攻击
I gave my word of honor and he will not be molested!
这是命令
And that's a direct order!
那你另外找个送货人
You can just get yourself another delivery boy.
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
- 这不是回家的路 - 去冰激凌工厂看怎么生产冰激凌
- This isn't the right way! - We're going to the ice cream factory.
谁不想去可以在这儿下车
Anyone doesn't want to, can get off.
我要回家找妈妈
I want to go home to my mother.
你想回家找谁
Go home to your what?
给我唱歌 唱
Now, sing! Sing again!
怎么了 为什么不唱 快唱
What's the matter? Don't you sing?
为什么不唱 病了吗
Are you sick? What is it?
要是不唱 你们的妈妈都得死
Sing or your mothers will die!
我要把你们的妈妈都杀死
I'll kill your mothers! And the rest of you!
并入右车道
Get in the right-hand lane.
那样对待他们不对
Not right to treat children that way.
- 会把他们吓坏的 - 只管开好这该死的车
- You'll hurt them. - Just drive the goddamn bus!
并入右车道
And get in the right-hand lane!
我要妈妈
I want my mother.
弗朗西斯大道
The sign, Sir Drake Blvd.
向右
Make a right there.
牌子在那里
There's a sign to Sir Drake Boulevard!
- 朝那边开 - 我知道
- Head to it. - I know.
不是这个
Not this one.
我要妈妈
I want my mother.
闭嘴
Shut up!
向右开
Just get to the right!
天哪
Jesus!
他在那里干什么
What the hell is he doing up there?
你干什么 超过那辆车
What the hell are you doing? Pass the V.W., will you?
你以为你在干什么
What the hell you thinking you are doing?
把枪扔掉
Drop the gun, creep!
我会把他脑袋打飞
I'll blow his brains out.
把该死的枪扔掉
Drop the fucking gun!
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
他打了6枪还是5枪
You're thinking, did he fire 6 shots, or only 5?
说实话我自己也忘了
To tell you the truth, I forgot myself, in all this excitement.
不过这是世界上最厉害的手枪
But being this is a.44 Magnum, the most powerful handgun in the world...
能把你的脑袋打飞
...and will blow your head clean off...
你得问自己
...you've got to ask yourself:
"我走运吗"
"Do I feel lucky?"
你走运吗 混蛋
Well, do you, punk?